Expert: You know, to be honest, I think you’re being a bit hard on him.
I mean, he’s only twenty-five.
It’s good that he has a job, and everybody needs a holiday.
My advice is that you should let him go to Mexico, but when he comes back,
you should sit down with him and talk to him about starting to pay rent.
That way he’ll understand that he needs to start planning for the future and
to start thinking about renting a flat.
But I know from talking to other parents that there are a lot of young people
still living at home in their twenties and thirties, and some of them don’t even have jobs.
So in many ways, I think you’re lucky.
Annabel: You see? That’s just what I think…